# Aimee Blake

## Registered Nurse Assistant Nurse Manager/ Supervisor - Daughters of Sarah

Albany, NY 12205 ablake6418@gmail.com 518-852-7574

Ambitious nurse with 3 years-experience working in a variety of nursing settings during my career. Team player eager to help provide quality patient care, excelling in communication, time management and leadership skills.

## Work Experience

### Registered Nurse Assistant Nurse Manager/ Supervisor

Daughters of Sarah - New York, NY September 2018 to Present

Provide nursing care to individuals on the rehabilitation unit and assist with admissions and discharges.

- \*Communicate with doctors and assisting with provider visits and submitting orders in computer.
- \*Supervising staff and providing leadership during shift

## **Registered Nurse**

Samaritan Hospital - New York, NY March 2018 to September 2018

Provide nursing care to medical surgical patients including assessments, medication passes, and treatments.

\*Ensuring HIPAA compliance while providing care.

#### **Registered Nurse**

Nathan Littauer Hospital - New York, NY July 2016 to March 2018

Provide nursing care to patients during labor, delivery and the postpartum period.

\*Primary care, assessment and evaluation of neonatal and maternal patients.

### **Direct Support Professional**

Lexington ARC - New York, NY February 2013 to August 2016

Direct care to individuals with physical and developmental disabilities.

- \*Assisting with activities of daily living, cooking meals, assisting with eating, transporting individuals.
- \*Passing medications, g-tube feedings, testing blood sugars, administering insulin.

#### Education

### **Bachelors in Nursing**

Suny Delhi State University of New York

# Associate of Science in Applied Science, Nursing

Fulton Montgomery Community College 2016

## **Associates in Liberal Arts**

Fulton Montgomery Community College 2011

# **Nursing Licenses**

### RN

Expires: May 2022

State: NY

# Skills

Med Surg, Home Health, RN